{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4972","name":"Punch Bowl 360 Bar","address":"1331 Broadway","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Robert Thompson","licenseNumber":"079691","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.04660,42.33464","geojson":{"id":"4972","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.046597177,42.3346405520001]},"properties":{"name":"Punch Bowl 360 Bar","owner":"Robert Thompson","address":"1331 Broadway","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"079691","establishmentid":"4972","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/13/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3404","name":"Vicente's Cuban Cuisine","address":"1250 Library St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4667","name":"Bert's on Broadway DBA Rockefellers","address":"1315 Broadway","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5200","name":"The Skip","address":"1234 Library St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5337","name":"I Luv Cheese","address":"1368 Broadway","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4869","name":"7 Greens","address":"1222 Library St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5031","name":"Standby","address":"225 Gratiot Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4427","name":"Steve's Detroit Deli","address":"212 E Grand River","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4906","name":"Jose's Tacos, LLC","address":"218 E Grand River","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4106","name":"Detroit Seafood Market","address":"1435 Randolph","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4844","name":"Centre Park Restaurant","address":"1407 Randolph","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4146","name":"CK Mediterranean Grille","address":"119 Monroe St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4631","name":"Cottage Inn Pizza","address":"107 Monroe St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3387","name":"Jimmy Johns","address":"95 Monroe St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3269","name":"Orchid Thai","address":"115 Monroe St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4317","name":"Colors","address":"311 E Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1043","name":"Ted's Cafe DBA The Baltimore","address":"1234 Randolph St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1681","name":"Hilton Garden Inn/ American Grill","address":"351 Gratiot Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5226","name":"Calexico","address":"1040 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5103","name":"Detroit Water Ice Factory ","address":"1014 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5327","name":"Detroit Water Ice Factory","address":"1014 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"45054","inspectionDate":"2018-07-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"IMPROPER Sanitizer bucket","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above.e"},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Counter(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Counter(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Utensil storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."}]},{"inspectionid":"40913","inspectionDate":"2017-11-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Handwashing sinks are to be accessible for use at all times"}]},{"inspectionid":"38837","inspectionDate":"2017-05-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Dishwasher (glass washer)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/Replace"},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Utensil storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."}]},{"inspectionid":"37055","inspectionDate":"2016-11-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"At the Bare hand contact","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"At the SANITIZING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"At the Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"In water less than 135 degrees f","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Utensil storage","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain water at 135 degrees F or greater."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Dishwasher","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4972"}}